A Guide to the Lewis F. Powell Jr. Papers, 1929-1998
Washington and Lee University, School of Law, Lewis F. Powell, Jr. Archives
- Personal Papers 1921-1996
  - Speeches, Statements, and Writings 1937-1971
    - Speeches, Statements and Writings
      - The Ideological Assault On America, November 17, 1970 (Box-folder 118/4)
        Convocation Address, Longwood College, Farmville, Virginia.
      - Executives' Secretaries, Inc., February 11, 1971 (Box-folder 118/5)
        Richmond Chapter.
      - Organized Crime and Electronic Surveillance - In Virginia, April 15, 1971 (Box-folder 118/6)
        Bar Association of the City of Richmond, Richmond, Virginia.
      - End of an Era and New Horizons, May 12, 1971 (Box-folder 118/7)
        United Virginia Bankshares Meeting, Williamsburg, Virginia.
      - Repression of Civil Liberties - Fact or Fiction?, June 28, 1971 (Box-folder 118/8)
        Published in June 28, 1971 Perspectives section of Richmond Times-Dispatch
      - City of Richmond - Chesterfield Annexation, Applicability of Voting Rights Act, August 9, 1971 (Box-folder 118/9)
        Submitted informally to the Attorney General.
      - Attack On American Free Enterprise System, August 23, 1971 (Box-folder 118/10)
        Confidential Memorandum to Eugene B. Sydnor, Jr., Chairman Education Committee, U.S. Chamber of Commerce.
      - Virginia State Chamber of Commerce, December 17, 1971 (Box-folder 118/11)
        Notes for speech.
    - Papers re Speeches, Statements and Writings
      - Interposition March 29, 1956
        - Research Materials and Notes, January-March 1956 (Box-folder 119/1)
        - Drafts, March 1956 (Box-folder 119/2-4)
          16 rpm audio recording disc containing a dictated draft is stored separately for preservation purposes.
        - Clippings, 1955-1956 (Box-folder 119/5-6)
      - Hampden-Sydney College (6/8/59), February-June 1959 (Box-folder 119/7)
      - New Orleans Bar Association (9/11/62), March-August 1962 (Box-folder 119/8)
      - What State Bar Ecomomics Committees Can Do(ABA; 1/23/63), January 1963 (Box-folder 119/9)
      - NACCA Bar Association (8/5/63), May-July, 1963 (Box-folder 119/10)
      - Conference of National Organizations (3/10/64), January-April 1964 (Box-folder 119/11)
      - American College of Trial Lawyers (3/14-18/64), March 14-18, 1964 (Box-folder 119/12)
      - Reflections On the Crime Problem(4/14/64), July 1963-April 1964 (Box-folder 119/13)
      - Howard College (4/18/64), August 1963-April 1964 (Box-folder 119/14)
      - Kentucky State Bar Associatin (4/22/64), October 1963-April 1964 (Box-folder 119/15)
      - University of South Carolina (5/1/64), July 1963-May 1964 (Box-folder 119/16)
      - Barristers' Luncheon (5/20/64), March-May 1964 (Box-folder 119/17)
      - Peaceful Coexistence(5/26/64), May 15, 1964 (Box-folder 119/18)
      - Indigent Defendants(6/5-6/64), June 1-5, 1964 (Box-folder 120/1)
      - Montana Bar Association (6/11-13/64), September 1963-June 1964 (Box-folder 120/2)
      - Pennsylvania Bar Association (6/24-25/64), December 1963-July 1964 (Box-folder 120/3)
      - Virginia State Bar (7/2-5/64), February-July 1964 (Box-folder 120/4)
      - International Bar Association - Mexico City (7/25-31/64), November 1963-August 1964 (Box-folder 120/5)
      - National Institute of Bar Public Relations (8/7/64), December 1963-July 1964 (Box-folder 120/6)
      - Jamestown Foundation (5/20/64), (8/20/64), July-August 1964 (Box-folder 120/7)
      - Federal Bar Association (9/10/64), July-September 1964 (Box-folder 120/8)
      - Indiana Bar (9/18/64), August 1963-September 1964 (Box-folder 120/9)
      - State Bar of Michigan (9/25/64), September 1963-September 1964 (Box-folder 120/10)
      - New Mexico Bar Association (10/2/64), September 1963-October 1964 (Box-folder 120/11)
      - West Virginia Bar (10/16/64), September-October 1964 (Box-folder 120/12)
      - Seminar on the Need for Education About Communism (Atlanta; 10/22/64), June-October 1964 (Box-folder 120/13)
      - Prentice Hall, Inc. (10/27/64), September-October 1964 (Box-folder 121/1)
      - Boston Univesity (10/29/64), July-October 1964 (Box-folder 121/2)
      - Nebraska Bar (11/12/64), May-July 1964 (Box-folder 121/3)
      - Oklahoma Bar Association (12/4/64), January-December 1964 (Box-folder 121/4)
      - American Farm Bureau Federation (12/9/64), September 1964-January 1965 (Box-folder 121/5)
      - Texas Bill of Rights Foundation (12/15/64), September--December 1964 (Box-folder 121/6)
      - University of Virginia School of Law (12/18/64), October-December 1964 (Box-folder 121/7)
      - Association of American Law Schools (12/28/64), April-December 1964 (Box-folder 121/8)
      - South Florida Inter-Professinal Council (1/7/65), December 1964-January 1965 (Box-folder 121/9)
      - Dade County Bar Association (1/11/65), October 1964-January 1965 (Box-folder 121/10)
      - Maryland State Bar Association (1/15/65), October 1964-January 1965 (Box-folder 121/11)
      - New York State Bar Association (1/29/65), September 1964-June 1965 (Box-folder 121/12)
      - ABA New Orleans (2/7/65), September 1964-February 1965 (Box-folder 122/1)
      - Cincinnati Bar Association (2/23/65), 1963, February 1965 (Box-folder 122/2)
      - Cleveland Bar Association (3/4/65), 1962-March 1965 (Box-folder 122/3)
      - San Francisco Bar Association (3/23/65), November 1964-June 1965 (Box-folder 122/4)
      - Los Angeles Bar Association (3/25/65), December 1964-April 1965 (Box-folder 122/5)
      - Southern Electric Exchange (3/29/65), September 1964-March 1965 (Box-folder 122/6)
      - American College of Trial Lawyers (4/5/65), October 1964-April 1965 (Box-folder 122/7)
      - Louisiana State Bar (4/22/65), March 1964-May 1965 (Box-folder 122/8)
      - University of Florida (4/26/65), May 1964-December 1965 (Box-folder 122/9)
      - Missouri Bar Center (5/1/65), May 1964-July 1965 (Box-folder 122/10)
      - Notre Dame University (5/3/65), June 1964-September 1965 (Box-folder 122/11)
      - Atlanta Bar Association (5/7/65), May 1964-June 1965 (Box-folder 122/12)
      - Arkansas Bar Association (6/3/65), March 1964-July 1965 (Box-folder 123/1)
      - Wichita State University (6/8/65), September 1964-March 1965 (Box-folder 123/2)
      - National Conference On Law and Poverty (6/25/65), April-July 1965 (Box-folder 123/3)
      - Fourth Circuit Judicial Conference (6/26/65), July 1964-1968 (Box-folder 122/4)
      - North Carolina Bar Association (6/29/65), September 1964-July 1965 (Box-folder 123/5)
      - Texas Bar Association (7/1/65), September 1964-July 1965 (Box-folder 123/6)
      - Ninth Circuit Judicial Conference (7/15/65), March-July 1965 (Box-folder 123/7)
      - American Bar Association (8/9/65), 1962-August 1965 (Box-folder 123/8-9)
      - American Bar Foundation (8/10/65), 1962-July 1965 (Box-folder 123/10)
      - Canadian Bar Association (9/1/65), October 1964-September 1965 (Box-folder 124/1)
      - Committee for Effective and Durable Peace In Asia, August-November 1965 (Box-folder 124/2)
      - Virginia Association of Colleges (2/25/66), July 1965-July 1966 (Box-folder 124/3)
      - Washington and Lee Law Review(3/66), November 1965-March 1966 (Box-folder 124/4)
      - Washington and Lee University, A Lawyer Looks At Civil Disobedience, April 16, 1966
        - Correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 124/5)
        - Draft, April 11, 1966 (Box-folder 124/6)
        - Reading Copy, April 16, 1966 (Box-folder 124/7)
        - Galley Proofs, September 8, 1966 (Box-folder 124/8)
        - Research Materials, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 124/9-11)
      - International Bar Association -- Switzerland (7/66), December 1965-July 1966 (Box-folder 125/1-4)
      - Wake Forest College School of Law (10/21/66), May-October 1966 (Box-folder 125/5)
      - National Conference of Bar Presidents (2/10/67) (Box-folder 125/6)
      - Business Council (5/13/67), May-October 1966
        - Correspondence, March-October 1967 (Box-folder 125/7)
        - Research materials and reading copy of speech, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 125/8)
      - Harvard University Class Reunion (5/20/67), February-July 1967 (Box-folder 125/9)
      - Conference of Financial Executives (6/17/67), April-June 1967 (Box-folder 125/10)
      - National Conference of Bar Presidents (8/5/67), May-August 1967 (Box-folder 125/11)
      - National Legal Aid and Defenders Association (8/6/67), May-July 1966 (Box-folder 125/12)
      - ABA Meeting (Hawaii) (8/8/67), April-July 1967 (Box-folder 125/13)
      - Richmond Jaycees (7/7/67), July-September 1967 (Box-folder 126/1)
      - The Southern Company Meeting, Point Clear Alabama, October 5 1967
        Civil Disobedience: Prelude to Revolution?
        - Correspondence September 1967-January 1968 (Box-folder 126/2-5)
        - Reading copy of speech, October 2 1967 (Box-folder 126/6)
        - Clippings and Pamphlet, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 126/7)
      - Dun's Review interview (4/16/68), February-June 1968 (Box-folder 126/8)
      - Virginia Retail Merchants' Association, May 20, 1968
        - Correspondence, October 1967-August 1968 (Box-folder 126/9)
        - Speech Draft, May 9 1968-May 16, 1968 (Box-folder 126/10)
        - Research Materials, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 126/11-13)
      - International Bar Association (7/68), November 1967-April 1968 (Box-folder 127/1)
        Powell changed plans and did not speak at this event.
      - Fourth Circuit Judicial Conference (7/68), November 1967-May 1968 (Box-folder 127/2)
      - American Association of State Colleges and Universities, (11/11/68), June 1968-March 1969 (Box-folder 127/3)
      - Chamber of Commerce, Kenbridge, Virginia (2/27/69), February 18-28, 1969 (Box-folder 127/4)
      - Thomas Jefferson Award (10/3/69), April 1969-March 1970 (Box-folder 127/5)
      - Comments on the Vietnamese War, Richmond Junior League (2/11/1970), January 1970 (Box-folder 127/6)
      - An Education Program FOR America(5/28/70), May-June 1970 (Box-folder 127/7)
      - The Attack on American Institions, Southern Industrial Relations Conference (7/15/70), 1966-1970 (Box-folder 127/8)
      - Law Enforcement Banquet (10/12/70), July-October 1970 (Box-folder 127/9)
      - Longwood College Convocation (11/17/70), September 1970-January 1971 (Box-folder 127/10)
      - Wiretapping Bill Testimony (4/15/70), February-April 1971 (Box-folder 127/11)
      - End of an Era and New Horizons, United Virginia Bankshares Meeting (5/12/71), March 23-May 1971 (Box-folder 127/12)
      - Civil Liberties Repression: Fact or Fiction? g, July-October 1971 (Box-folder 127/13-14)
      - Attack on American Free Enterprise System(8/23/71), May-October 1971 (Box-folder 127/15)
      - Digest of Max Radin ABA Journal Articles, n.d. (Box-folder 127/16)
    - Research Materials
      Arranged alphabetically by topic.
      - Civil Disobedience 1966-1967 (Box-folder 128/1)
      - Civil Liberties Repression 1970-1971 (Box-folder 128/2-3)
      - Communism and Soviet Education, c. 1958-1963 (Box-folder 128/4)
      - Criminal Justice, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 128/5-7)
      - Electronic Surveillance, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 129/1)
      - English Courts and Criminal Justice, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 129/2)
      - Interposition, 1955-1957 (Box-folder 129/3)
      - Organized Crime, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 129/4)
      - Professional Responsibility and Discipline of the Bar, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 129/5)
- Military Service Papers 1942-1994
  The subgroup Military Service Papers, (3 cu.ft.) includes series of records and papers concerning: World War II; Powell's postwar military associations; and his participation in historical studies of World War II.
  - World War II Service 1942-1947
    World War II Service series, includes subseries of diaries, a record volume, Powell's "201" file, correspondence, reports, training materials, and printed materials and memorabilia. The Post World War II series includes subseries dealing with the Air Force Association and the Air Force Reserve.
    - Diaries 1942-1944 (Box-folder 130/1-7)
    - Correspondence 1942-1947 (Box-folder 130/8, Box-folder 131/1-9)
    - Record Volume 1942-1946 (w. 1984 annotations) (Box-folder 130/10)
    - "201" File 1942-1946 & n.d. (Box-folder 131/12-14, Box-folder 132/1-4)
    - Reports 1943-1948 (Box-folder 132/6-12)
    - Training Materials 1942-1943 (Box-folder 132/13-17, Box-folder 133/1-15, Box-folder 134/1-4)
    - Intelligence Papers re North Africa 1942-1943 (Box-folder 134/5-15)
    - London Apartment 1944-1945 (Box-folder 134/16-17)
    - German Captured War Documents 1941-1944 (translated 1947) (Box-folder 134/18)
    - Memorabilia 1943-1946 (Box-folder 134/19, Box Oversize Folder 9)
    - Printed Material 1945 (Box-folder 135/1-2, Box Oversize Folder 9)
  - Post-World War II Service 1946-1985
    - Air Force Association 1946-1985 (Box-folder 136/1-7)
    - Air Force Reserve 1947-1949 (Box-folder 136/8-13)
  - World War II Historical Studies 1962-1996
    Historical Studies & Interviews contains materials from thirty years and more after Powell left active service. The allies' ability to break the German Ultra code remained a U.S. government security classified secret until the mid-1970's. Powell never spoke or wrote about these activities during this period of secrecy. When the activities of Powell and his cohorts became declassified public knowledge, there followed a period of intense interest on the part of the news media and historians.
    Finally able to talk publicly, Powell eagerly corresponded with historians and former associates. He offered several authors extensive assistance and granted oral history interviews in his Supreme Court chambers. One of these projects culminated in the publication of Ultra and the Army Air Forces in World War II. This work, subtitled An Interview with Associate Justice of the U.S. Supreme Court Lewis F. Powell, Jr., was published by the Office of Air Force History. Memoranda, notes and diary entries from the first series of this subgroup appear as appendices in this book.
    - Correspondence 1962-1994 (Box-folder 136/14-25, Box-folder 137/1-2)
    - B-26 Marauder Society 1988-1992 (Box-folder 137/3-4)
    - 319th Bomb Group 1974-1996 (Box-folder 137/6-9)
    - Dresden Bombing 1945, 1978-1987 (Box-folder 137/10-15)
    - Carl A. Spaatz Biography 1982-1988 (Box-folder 137/16-23)
    - Ultra 1944-1945; 1984-1994
      - Correspondence 1984-1994 (Box-folder 137/25-29, Box-folder 138/1-22)
      - Ultra and the Army Air Forces in World War II 1985-1987 (Box-folder 138/23-27, Box-folder 139/1-4)
      - Freeburg Project 1985 (Box-folder 139/4-7)
      - Research Materials 1944-1945; 1974-1995
        - Contemporary Documents 1944-1945 (Box-folder 139/8-15, Box-folder 140/1-5)
        - Articles 1977-1984 (Box-folder 140/6-)
        - Clippings 1945, 1974-1995 (Box-folder 140/7-9)
- Law Firm (Hunton & Williams) Records 1945-1972 (Box 36-51)
  Though Powell spent thirty-eight years at Hunton & Williams the subgroup, Law Firm (Hunton & Williams) Records (5.5 cu. ft.), is not extensive. For reasons of client confidentiality and corporate records management, all of his client files remained with the firm's records. (For records of Powell's lawyering, see the civic and corporate series of the Board Memberships subgroup.) What can be found here is a small series of correspondence on two specific topics, memoranda, a forms file containing exemplar legal documents, some few firm financial statements, and "housekeeping" records. This last mentioned series contains what are potentially the most interesting materials in the subgroup. The "Time Tickets, 1956-1971" form a record of how Powell expended his billable and pro bono hours. His personal calendars show his appointments from 1949 to 1971.
  - Correspondence
    - World War II, 1942 (Box-folder 141/1-)
    - Remodling of Office, 1954 (Box-folder 141/2-)
    - Re Death of T. Justin Moore, 1958 (Box-folder 141/3-)
  - Memoranda
    - General, 1939, 1945-1972. (Box-folder 141/4-34, Box-folder 142/1-28, Box-folder 143/1-22)
    - ABA Expenses, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 143/23-37)
    - Hunton & Williams History, 1977 (Box-folder 143/38)
    - Re Firm Partnership, 1956-1971 (Box-folder 144/1-10)
  - Partnership Agreements 1955-1971 (Box-folder 144/11-14)
  - Forms File 1945-1951 & n.d. (Box-folder 144/15-27)
    This subseries comprises exemplar contracts and other legal instruments.
  - Financial Statements
    - Monthly Earnings, 1952-1954 (Box-folder 145/1-3)
    - Year Ending, 1949-1953 & 1970 (Box-folder 145/4-11)
  - Housekeeping Records
    - Address Books
      - Book #1, 1954 (Box-folder 145/12-16)
      - Book #2, c. 1964 (Box-folder 145/17-21)
    - File Indices
      - File Index #1, 1950-1972 (Box-folder 145/22-23)
      - File Index #2, 1959 (Box-folder 145/24-29)
      - File Index #3, c. 1965 (Box 146)
        These are index cards. The other two indicies are in book format.
    - Calendars
      - Desk 1949-1971 (Box 147-151)
      - Pocket 1957-1970 (Box 152)
    - Time Tickets, 1956-1971 (Box 153-160)
- Professional Associations 1937-1971
  The subgroup Professional Associations (35 cu. ft.) contains Powell's files concerning his memberships, and the offices he held, in a variety of legal associations.
  - American Bar Association 1937-1971 (Box 52-81)
    American Bar Association includes records from the time Powell joined the ABA's Junior Bar Conference in 1937 until he joined the Supreme Court. His extensive committee work records, alone, run some nine feet. Powell's service in a variety of offices is documented here. These include: chairman of the Junior Bar Conference; member of the House of Delegates and Board of Governors; president-elect; and president. There is also a long run of general correspondence from 1952 to 1971.
    Among the voluminous committee records, those pertaining to the Economics of Law Practice Committee are especially notable. Powell had a career long interest in improving law firm management, as can be seen in several of his speeches. The first ABA Lawyer's Handbook was published under Powell's chairmanship of this committee.
    The campaign that made Powell president-elect was hard fought, as had been his first election for the House of Delegates. It is interesting to note the similarities between the meticulous planning and the gathering of endorsements in these campaigns, and the later preparation for his Supreme Court nomination hearings. Powell may have learned important lessons in his work on the ABA presidential campaigns on behalf of his fellow Washington & Lee alumnus and friend Ross Malone. Records from these Malone campaigns are present, as well.
    Powell's presidential papers are dominated by documentation of the agenda he brought to this office: legal ethics reform, legal services to the poor and the establishment of standards for the administration of criminal justice. During his time in the ABA's top office, he also played a vital role in passage of the Twenty-fifth Amendment to the Constitution regarding presidential disability and succession.
    Powell also used his influence in the ABA as an opportunity to promote the establishment in schools and colleges of educational programs about communism. This is reflected, not only in his presidential papers, but throughout his ABA records. In 1961, Powell introduced a resolution in the House of Delegates calling for "adequate instruction in the history, doctrines, objectives and techniques of Communism." He chaired the special committee established to implement this resolution. In 1962, this committee published the pamphlet "Instruction on Communism and Its Contrast With Liberty Under Law." All of this is extensively documented here.
    Powell made hundreds of speeches as president-elect and president. He had these bound into two record volumes which are in this subseries. Volume II includes clippings. Hundreds of additional, loose clippings are here, as well.
    - Junior Bar Conference
      - Correspondence, 1937-1940 (Box-folder 161/1-36)
      - Subject Files, 1937-1942
        - Activities In Maryland 1937-1940 (Box-folder 162/1)
        - Activities In North Carolina 1937-1940 (Box-folder 162/2)
        - Activities In South Carolina 1937-1940 (Box-folder 162/3)
        - Activities In West Virginia 1937-1940 (Box-folder 162/4)
        - By-Laws c. 1935-1941 (Box-folder 162/5)
        - Re Chairmanship, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 162/6-7)
        - Circuits(Reports of Activities by Federal Judicial Circuit,) 1938-1942 (Box-folder 162/8-10)
          Circuits represented: Second, Third, Fourth, Seventh, Ninth & Tenth.
        - Committee Papers 1938-1941
          - Civil Liberties 1938 (Box-folder 162/11)
          - Defense of Liberties 1938-1941
            - Correspondence 1938-1940 (Box-folder 162/12-17, Box-folder 163/1-5)
            - Memoranda 1938-1939 (Box-folder 163/6)
            - Reports 1938-1939 & n.d. (Box-folder 163/7-9)
            - Speeches 1938-1941 (Box-folder 163/11)
            - Directories, 1939 & n.d. (Box-folder 163/12)
            - Clippings, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 163/13)
            - Printed Materials, 1935-1938 (Box-folder 163/14-15)
          - Restatements of the Law, 1936-1937 (Box-folder 163/16)
          - Supreme Court Proposal, 1937 (Box-folder 163/1-17)
        - Directories 1937-1941 (Box-folder 163/18)
        - Member of Council 1941-1942 (Box-folder 164/1-5)
        - Membership, 1937-1940 (Box-folder 164/6)
        - Minutes
          - General, 1939 (Box-folder 164/7)
          - Executive Council, 1937-1942 (Box-folder 164/8-9)
        - National Defense Program, 1940 (Box-folder 164/810)
        - News Bulletins, 1942 (Box-folder 164/11)
        - Programs, 1939, 1942 (Box-folder 164/12)
        - Public Information Programs
          - Memoranda, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 164/13)
          - Reports, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 164/14)
          - Directors of Public Information, n.d. (Box-folder 164/15)
          - Handbook, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 164/16)
          - Speeches, 1940-1941 & n.d. (Box-folder 164/17-25, Box-folder 165/1-16)
            Speeches are by others than Lewis F. Powell, Jr.
          - Printed Materials, 1941 & n.d. (Box-folder 165/17)
          - Questionnaire, n.d. (Box-folder 165/18)
          - Resolutions, 1938-1941 (Box-folder 165/19)
          - State Chairmen Meeting, 1940 (Box-folder 165/20)
          - Printed Materials, 1935-1941 (Box-folder 165/21-23)
    - General Correspondence 1952-1971 (Box-folder 167/11-45, Box-folder 166/11-25, Box-folder 168/1-25)
    - Subject Files
      - American Assembly On Law and Social Order 1967-1968 (Box-folder 168/26)
      - Russian Trip 1958
        - Diaries
          - Lewis F. Powell, Jr. 1958 (Box-folder 168/27-32)
          - Elizabeth A. Malone 1958 (Box-folder 168/33-34)
        - Itinerary 1958 (Box-folder 168/35)
        - Correspondence, 1958-1959 (Box-folder 168/36-43)
        - Speeches
          - Lewis F. Powell, Jr. 1958 (Box-folder 168/44)
          - Charles S. Rhyne, 1958 (Box-folder 168/45)
        - Interviews 1958 (Box-folder 168/46)
        - Clippings, 1958 (Box-folder 168/47)
    - Meetings
      - Annual 1956-1971
        - London 1957
          - Correspondence, 1956-1957 (Box-folder 169/1-7)
          - Speech - Contributory Negligence: A Necessary Check On the American Jury, July 26, 1957
            - Correspondence, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 169/8-15)
            - Memoranda, 1957 (Box-folder 169/16)
            - Research Materials, May-June 1957 (Box-folder 169/17-18)
            - Drafts, May-June, 1957 (Box-folder 169/19-22)
            - Summary and Printed Version, July 26, 1957 (Box-folder 169/23)
            - Harvard Law Record(12/11/58) version, February 18, 1958 (Box-folder 169/24)
              Titled Questions of Comparative Negligence